oh now that I now that I remember antes de que se me olvide .
this lady from the school .
mmhm .
she told me she told me that she bought the subway passes for the whole year .
subway passes to where to New_York ?
to New_York it' forty bucks .
yeah but you know what she bought I told you she bought that pass .
which one ?
it' a special pass that they give .
um .
it' a special pass .
it' called something and it gives you also discounts to certain museums in New_York .
it' like a ...
but for the whole year ?
yeah con ese pase you can you know you can use it and you can you have certain discounts .
but it comes out more expensive doesn't it .
I don't know she says she can use it up and down as many times as she wants .
like I would ...
was she gonna give it to you ?
I wonder if it has a picture .
I should ask her .
I don't know .
I don't know because I saw that .
they talk about it .
it' called something .
it' like a a supersaver I don't know what .
and I was like why do they keep on referencing this ?
I wonder what it is .
but she just told me as in subway only .
yes for the subway .
it' for the it' it' for that .
but there may be something different that she bought .
because this one serves as as a as a thing for the subway .
but it also gives you if you have that card sometimes you can get into certain museums and things like that .
pero bueno I checked out the prize and I was like if we are just gonna use .
she told me she paid forty two dollars or forty dollars or something like that .
It' like using the metro here and you buy the annual pass it comes out cheaper .
.
ay yo sabía .
ay Dios mío .
tú eres de madre .
that was Katherine Hart by the way .
laugh .
whoever wants to know .
the .
laugh .
qué vergüenza !
yo sabía .
I'm gonna kill her .
laugh .
.
y él los oye .
eh ?
él los escucha .
ahora me mandaron un ...
tú por fin did you book the hotel for September ?
no .
porque me mandaron ahora un special el western de Times_Square in one seventy nine .
but they only have one day in September .
one day ?
one day .
Paige yo no sabía que a María la estaban recording también .
eh .
que a María la estaban recording también .
María is on all day .
yeah I saw her with that thing .
I thought it was her I_Pod .
and I go .
what kind of I_Pod is that ?
and then miré miré bien .
y dije .
no ella debe estar haciendo otra cosa .
yeah because her sister does no sé qué cosa .
yeah he explained it to me that she' doing a more extensive one .
hers is thirty hours .
wow .
she has to be recorded or something .
imagínate tú thirty hours .
she' been at it for a long time too .
imagínate thirty hours is almost a week with it .
so what eh bueno so I went to go check for you .
and they only have one day in in in September that you can get discount .
I'm just gonna go and ...
pero que tengo que esperar a a coger el dinero ese en mayo .
qué dinero ?
el dinero ese que nos van a dar with the taxes .
oh ok .
and I'm still four months ahead .
yeah .
eh I mean how much it'll probably go up yeah second month to the first .
tengo un dolor de cabeza de perros .
what did you eat yesterday que te cayó mal ?
I went to Publix yesterday night .
and I did some shopping .
y I didn't wanna cook .
o_k .
so I made that' turkey and stuffing and macaroni and cheese .
yo no sé por qué tú comes macaroni and cheese si tú sabes que te va a caer mal .
siempre te cae mal .
no no no something something happened something that chicken .
chicken but what' wrong with the chicken ?
the the turkey I don't know me dio un asco .
but what kind of turkey was it ?
desmenuzado con stuffing todo mezclado .
you got that at Publix .
yeah .
sounds good .
it did .
it looked good .
y no te dio asco or something .
don't throw up now .
because then I gotta go with you .
laugh .
to the bathroom .
and I don't wanna be .
no thank you .
pero my god .
sigh it' hot .
found that thing for the for the wine thing expensive .
fifty dollars .
for two hours it' twenty five bucks an hour .
unless you drink like a fish it' it' good to go .
he' like I would wanna go .
pero there' a whole bunch of restaurants participating .
what I wanted to ask Adelina was .
is that the one that they was doing in Coral_Gables that they closed it down ?
I've never seen it before .
I think so .
I've seen it in a in a in a .
maybe like I bumped into it going home since it' on my way .
and I noticed that the streets are closed .
I yes and and and John has gone to it .
but I wanted to ask Adelina because they have a list of +//.
it says it says that they are gonna be serving .
there' gonna be wine right obviously .
mmhm .
but it' gonna be .
por cincuenta pesos ?
exactly from from this place Wild_Oats or something right ?
oh no .
espérate .
but then I'm saying fifty dollars !
and are you gonna get hors_d'oeuvres ?
but then I went into the restaurant section .
and it has all the restaurants participating .
so I'm like bueno is each restaurant gonna have like a booth that you can sample their food porque está Flemmings ahí .
no yeah Wild_Oats is not a ...
ok or are they just gonna pass the stupid hors_d'oeuvres and that' it por cincuenta pesos .
it' a healthy store .
no hay manera que tú te puedas tomar .
cincuenta .
bueno they're gonna have premium drinks too .
you know .
it doesn't sound bad though .
but I don't know .
I wanted to go .
but then Rafi was like .
John ha ido .
but then we had we left the girls yesterday to go to do the taxes .
so Rafi' like .
I don't know if I wanna leave the girls again you know .
so I don't know .
your mom' gonna mind .
I don't know .
I have to ask her .
y después que le grité hoy .
no y después que te .
laugh .
it' only for two hours anyway .
we are gonna be right there .
you know .
because he says .
it sounds good I've always wanted to go .
I always wanted to go to the one in South_Beach .
but the one South_Beach is so expensive .
that' two hundred dollars .
yeah it' really expensive .
and they keep on and they keep on .
that' ridiculous .
but my brother told me it' .
they keep on hiring the prize thinking that people are not gonna go .
and more people go .
and the people are going .
yeah .
now next year it'll be three hundred bucks .
but I'm gonna tell my brother next year para que me dé los tickets .
and here but here in here in miracle here in this one ?
they have a V_I_P for one fifty .
that you go in the tent .
and I don't know what they give you .
is Adelina here ?
I've seen the tent .
yeah let' go there .
I've seen that tent .
Sharon .
el el food festival ese .
.
ellos dijeron que iban a dar appetizers at Wild_Oats .
pero hay comida ?
.
entonces todos esos restaurants that are participating will have booths .
and they are provide food for you free .
.
oh ok because if they're just giving appetizers .
John has gone .
eh ?
no they have a list of the restaurants that are participating .
.
it' just in the little thing where you buy the ticket .
it tells you no eh you know the wine and premium drinks and hors_d'oeuvres from Wild_Oats .
I'm like ...
y Wild_Oats es un un healthy store ?
sí pero they have everything más o menos .
but still I mean you know it' hors_d'oeuvres it' just ...
I mean ...
.
I'm sure they probably have a sampling no ?
when you do that thing .
que everybody has .
.
yeah but you are paying for that right .
that' probably what it is .
ah bueno pero mientras que todo el mundo tenga .
porque estaba hasta el Flemmings y todo .
.
y va a estar there' a whole bunch of them .
Archies pizza that Archies place pizza and ...
oye tú no tienes que recoger a la niña ?
.
qué hora es ?
fifteen .
oh .
vamos saltando para allá .
qué andas haciendo ?
.
sneeze .
quién ?
who who' that ?
she' probably pregnant isn't she ?
she knows you ?
.
she is lying .
so how'd you add her ?
she' browsing .
.
ella se mete donde se mete la mamá de .
y después te manda todas estas manos de de cosas ahí .
.
no .
Rafi' mom también se mete en todas esas cosas .
laugh .
te vas a el papel ese ?
ay no .
laugh .
it' just fine .
ay pero vete a vomitar .
no y no hables de eso .
laugh .
oh my goodness .
what is that ?
nice to even to have your attention now you dirty sneaky immoral .
unfaithful doubts .
oh my god what ?
.
qué website ?
oh I don't know .
I have it um ...
just do the Core_Gables food and wine festival .
lost dog mira esto .
last humping his wife best friend on hidden camera answer to Steven to see the old dog participating tricks .
oh my god .
sigh .
oh my god that' terrible .
look at what she did .
gasp .
and a B_M_W .
she passed it .
inside the car .
gasp .
oh .
ay dios mío .
I think she is mad .
la mato .
gasp .
.
no you have to show her the other one .
look at what she did to that car .
no repitas .
no lo repitas .
no lo repitas alto .
a killer .
look at what she did laughs .
no, look at the other one .
dale .
laugh .
.
ay dios mío mira esto .
laugh .
y esto ?
.
ay dios mío how embarrassing !
oh my god .
did you find it ?
.
pero dónde tú estás buscando ?
estás metida en Tag .
qué es eso ?
son un website there .
son ...
ya yo ni me meto ahí .
sí ya vi ya .
todo el mundo quiere saber dónde dónde comprar el el delantal .
en qué nos metemos ?
ay está comiquísimo .
I got like six comments on the thing .
that is hilarious .
everybody wants to know .
that is I am gonna go look at it .
stop .
everybody wants to go .
everybody wants to see .
ella los vio ?
sí she said it was ...
she says those last two pictures was a bit disturbing .
and I said .
oh god I sent those out .
I wasn't supposed to .
lo encontraste o no ?
ah no .
igual que Carla no ha hecho nada .
Carla estaba de madre .
y ya porque como ella está en el chisme lado .
I think .
ay qué bueno .
dónde ?
oh Maggie mira Maggie has more than me .
qué es esto .
qué es eso qué es ?
is that the noise coming from there ?
the dog sniffing ?
I don't know .
I guess they have something wrong here .
oh it' probably that no ?
este manda unas cosas tan +//.
ellas con sus angelitos están de madre .
I go to the main page go to your main page in .
tienes que cambiar eso .
it and I can't open it .
mira para allá .
ay .
laugh .
ahí arriba ahí arriba .
oh .
laugh .
you go in .
and then you and you redo it .
go in the countdown .
and redo it .
how and I did .
right there press it .
and they do not no longer have it .
I tried it .
what do you mean ?
or there go the that one .
sí .
right there click the link .
no no there .
here ?
wait there .
now pick one .
wait hold on .
something .
yeah .
I wanna see them .
pick .
pick like My_space flowers or ...
ay qué lindo está ese .
ok .
enter the date .
it will be ...
may .
ninth .
two thousand and eight .
and then you put what you want .
New_York trip .
no te cabe .
ah .
just .
gross .
no .
put girl .
I know what I'm gonna do .
and gap .
.
now what do I do ?
eh ?
lo qué ?
and now what do I do ?
go down a minute .
and let me see that quick post .
oh I'll tell you where .
ok copy the thing .
copy .
ok now open My_space .
or should I copy it like that ?
yeah .
that' what I would do yeah .
that' gonna take forever .
ok .
yeah .
eh .
copy .
now go to your My_space .
now you have to go into going home .
.
profile about me ok .
go into profile there .
dónde ?
ahí mismo profile profile .
ahí ?
ahí .
about me .
ahora tienes que buscar el countdown .
imagínate tú .
debe estar en ...
go all the way down .
debe estar abajo .
I can más o menos ...
go down a ver .
yeah .
espérate espérate espérate .
counters .
let me see .
where does it say counters ?
here .
no no no .
ve arriba arriba .
to the top .
this is ...
does it say something countdown ?
yeah there it is .
.
dónde ?
no ves New_York ?
pero ahora no sé ...
at ok go sí I know pero it doesn't start there .
éste mira el countdown aquí está .
it probably starts all the way on the top .
go down a minute .
because you have to ...
countdowns .
oh it starts all the way there then .
es de aquí para arriba no ?
mira bien en la página donde está el countdown cómo empieza .
you you took it away right .
the countdown no .
where is it ?
it' in the page .
just stick it under I where I like to meet .
and where is that ?
right there .
here ?
see how it starts .
see embedded type .
now look for the same thing on the top .
but then erase from there .
it doesn't have the same thing does it ?
nope .
no .
es que you might you might erase your background that' why .
ok .
así mismo lo pongo .
put previous section ahí .
there it is .
but that' not the one I picked .
oh it' down there .
look at it down there .
I don't know how to get rid of ...
are you gonna change your layout ?
no .
because I need it .
yeah go save the changes .
so now what I can do is .
now go to view my profile .
dónde está eso ?
ahí arriba .
right there in the corner .
arriba arriba arriba there .
ahora tienes que quitar el de arriba .
pero no sé ...
pero yo puedo volver a hacerlo de ahí mismo ?
I thought you could .
but you can't .
I'm gonna put the other one now .
oh just like mine that I have double .
you do ?
yeah I have two of them .
and now fun hearts .
qué romántico .
oh .
we are going in September .
.
no .
y por fin Peggy cogió el esto o no ?
five six seven .
no .
you have to change the year .
she' not going ?
at all ?
she she doesn't get it cheap .
did she go ...
when is she leaving for for the cruise ?
ay no I wanna go back .
how do I go back ?
.
god it' still three hundred and eleven days away .
laugh .
me muero .
oh my god .
that' a long time .
why ?
there is only three hundred and sixty five days of the year .
laugh .
that doesn't sound right .
it can't be three hundred days from now .
it' ...
right now we're in March .
April May June July August .
uno dos tres cuatro cinco .
no that' wrong .
six times thirty .
it' a hundred and eighty .
ok when finish .
no that' just that' not right .
finish putting it there and then .
it probably hasn't refreshed or ...
singing .
a hundred and sixty .
that' what I thought .
I was like hello .
copy .
.
I'm gonna go to ...
dónde ahora ?
profile no ?
home .
then profile .
y voy a ...
profile ahí abajo .
aquí ?
no aquí en éste en control panel tiene que ser .
ah en en .
sí but now I don't know which one is ...
lo voy a poner aquí abajo .
I'd like to meet .
and what I'll do is I'll separate it .
you think you will .
but I doubt it' separated .
yeah look .
ya .
preview .
ah pero tienes que sacar el de arriba .
yeah but now I gotta figure out how the heck to do that .
now .
go into save .
save all changes .
I wonder where the countdown begins for that one .
it should be the first thing .
I would wanna say to take off all of that until a ver .
.
go in the bottom a ver .
right there .
no that' your background .
that I know .
here ?
all that is your background .
go up go up .
yeah that' your .
este I think it' up to here .
from object all the way to c_countdown New_York New_York .
go down a little bit more .
go down .
I can't .
espérate .
where it says A H R .
aquí ?
hasta aquí .
hasta object .
no pero no quites la A esa .
no ?
al final .
no because that' probably the beginning of ...
everything everything starts when you are when you are .
aquí .
uhuh right .
no pero no quites la cosita esa .
ah .
no ahí ahí right .
.
lo coge .
ok so separate it .
espérate .
there .
yeah .
delete .
ay dios mío .
now do a preview .
not that one .
the bottom .
down .
see if it did it .
what is this ?
whatever we did we did it .
there you go .
go down .
we did it .
no pero qué es esto ?
there it is Paige .
oh ok ok .
y esto no me salió ?
that' who you use to do your background .
so that' gonna come out .
so entonces save all changes .
ay dios mío .
now go into view my profile on the top .
ok .
sniff .
singing there you go .
vieja mira la canción esa .
I know .
I gotta .
y todo eso de Hannah_Montana .
girls just wanna have fun .
dónde estaba música ?
cómo lo quito ?
no .
tiene que ir en música arriba .
here ?
no .
yeah .
and then you gotta find the ...
aquí pongo la la música .
yeah .
who sings that ?
Madonna .
girls just wanna have fun .
that' Cyndi_Louper .
right that' what I thought Cyndi_Louper right .
go back .
el nombre de la canción .
ay I don't know .
that thing is so annoying .
and you're not typing anything .
sometimes you can't even find the artist .
typing singing .
she may not even be there .
y dónde está la canción ?
now you gotta go into her site .
cuál ?
ésta ?
cualquiera porque now we don't know which one' which .
we don't know which one' true and which one' not .
they have material girls material girls .
material material .
but that' Madonna .
that' Madonna .
go back and try the other one .
let' see .
true colors .
I see your true colors .
ah so si no la tiene no la puedo coger .
uhuh .
es que yo no creo que ella tiene un site porque those are just people I think .
maybe is this a Chinese pop ?
nope .
digo I don't know how to go to that other site and like look for it you know .
you can go into top artist .
and search on the top .
and see .
but she' not a top artist any_more .
.
or you can do a ...
no se puede ni mover esto .
pero go down .
oh there you go .
eh nice glasses .
what up .
he' going to the airport .
en qué lo puedo ayudar ?
vas al aeropuerto ?
discúlpame .
it it sounds like you're saying escúpame .
escúpame .
laughing .
oh .
escúpame .
.
discúlpame .
laughing .
en qué te puedo ayudar ?
.
laughing .
that' just .
oh god .
dime .
.
sí ?
muy bien .
adiós pues entonces .
hasta luego .
passport office .
of course not it' never on .
it' never on .
nunca !
yeah nunca la tienes puesta .
laughing .
you are being recorded .
yes .
hello .
laughing .
.
why and then who ?
mmhm partners in crime .
M I A mean F I .
oh he' going to the airport .
laugh .
hiss .
and she doesn't even work here .
and I don't even work here .
and she knows .
laughing .
.
what is he talking about ?
qué es eso ?
is he making fun of my cups ?
oh .
laughing .
they're so small .
qué lindo !
I know like everybody who keeps coming to me and telling me are you teasing me .
you see .
like I have forty three days for my first one and a hundred and sixty two ...
tienes que quitar todo eso de Hannah_Montana ya .
ay I know .
dale go into ...
that' easy because you just have it in one section .
go into home .
look I'm jolly .
ay how nice .
go into home .
you should seem nauseated .
home .
go into profile .
eso está aquí abajo .
music under music borra todo lo que hay under music .
all the way down .
ya .
bueno .
oh so I can even add things in here huh .
of course you can add them anywhere .
that' where people that' where people add their slide shows and stuff .
oh podíamos empezar a jugar aquí .
you add them in different sections .
you don't have to add it in one place .
ya ahora view profile .
ahí arriba .
me duele la muela otra vez .
ya .
ah muy bien .
do it .
ah ya yo sé jugar con eso .
so now you have all that +//.
everything that you have come out on this side .
because you have nothing on this side .
yo voy a agregar .
all you have is under the general section .
eh ?
ya yo sé cómo jugar aquí .
voy ahora a mi casa .
y voy a cambiar todo si me acuerdo .
y la canción ...
you can just go and pick .
no la canción es a meterme ahí en music .
y ya .
no me voy de aquí que va no me puedo meter .
qué ?
tengo hambre .
qué pasó ?
que ya .
ok I think we are done .
where is that ?
Julio then here .
qué lindo !
now I'm gonna change it around .
now I know what to do .
I did mine already .
yeah I think New_York is old .
old news .
I need to clean it .
but now I know how to play .
old news .